Athletics, Department of; Records ua746
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Mens' Sports, 1954-1986; 4; 3 cubic ft.
  - Soccer, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 56)
  - Soccer, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 57)
  - Swimming, 1967-1977 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 58)
  - Swimming, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 59)
  - Swimming, 1967-1968 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 60)
  - Swimming, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 61)
  - Swimming, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 62)
  - Swimming, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 63)
  - Swimming, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 64)
  - Swimming includes history since 1967, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 65)
  - Swimming, 1973-1974 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 66)
  - Swimming, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 67)
  - Swimming, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 68)
  - Swimming, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 69)
  - Swimming, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 70)
  - Tennis, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 71)
  - Tennis, 1967-1968 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 72)
  - Tennis, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 73)
  - Tennis, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 74)
  - Tennis, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 75)
  - Tennis, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 76)
  - Tennis, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 77)
  - Tennis, 1973-1974 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 78)
  - Tennis, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 79)
  - Tennis, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 80)
  - Tennis, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 81)
  - Tennis, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 82)
  - Tennis, 1967-1974 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 83)
  - Tennis, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 84)
  - Tennis, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 85)
  - Tennis, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 86)
  - Tennis, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 87)
  - SUNYAC Tennis, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 88)
  - Tennis, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 89)
  - Track and Field, 1964-1977 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 90)
  - Track and Field, 1967-1968 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 91)
  - Track and Field, 1968-1969 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 92)
  - Track and Field, 1969-1970 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 93)
  - Track and Field, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 94)
  - Track and Field, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 95)
  - Track and Field, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 96)
  - Track and Field, 1973-1974 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 97)
  - Track and Field, 1974-1975 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 98)
  - Track and Field, 1975 May 3 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 99)
  - Track and Field, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 100)
  - Track and Field, 1976-1977 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 1)
  - Track and Field, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 2)
  - Track and Field Roster [Restricted], 2008-2009 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 3)
  - Volleyball, 1977-1978 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 4)
  - Wrestling, 1966-1973 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 5)
  - Wrestling, 1967-1968 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 6)
  - Wrestling, 1968-1969 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 7)
  - Wrestling Master Material for Wrestling Notebook, 1969 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 8)
  - Wrestling v.s. Wrestling Federation, 1969 May (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 9)
  - Wrestling Section II HS Coaches' list, Undated (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 10)
  - Wrestling 2nd E. Stroudsburg Tournment, 1968 November 22-23 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 11)
  - Wrestling, 1969-1970 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 12)
  - Sunyac Wrestling, 1970-1972 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 13)
  - Wrestling, 1970-1971 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 14)
  - Wrestling, 1971-1972 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 15)
  - Wrestling, 1972-1973 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 16)
  - Wrestling, 1973-1974 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 17)
  - Wrestling, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 18)
  - Wrestling, 1975-1976 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 19)
  - Wrestling, 1976-1977 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 20)
  - SUNYAC Wrestling, 1976-1977 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 21)
  - Wrestling, 1977-1978 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 22)
  - Wrestling, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 23)
  - SUNYAC Wrestling, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (4-Mens' Sports), Folder 24)
- Womens' Sports, 1965-1979; 5; 0.33 cubic ft.
  The files include annual reports, budget requests, team score books, seasonal sports schedules, Sports Press Guide, Sports News and View, and team rosters, relating to women's intercollegiate athletics
  - Basketball Scorebooks, 1965-1970 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 1)
  - Basketball, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 2)
  - Basketball, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 3)
  - Basketball, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 4)
  - Basketball, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 5)
  - Basketball, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 6)
  - Cheerleading, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 7)
  - Cross Country, 1978 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 8)
  - Field Hockey, 1966-1968 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 9)
  - Gymnastics, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 10)
  - Gymnastics, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 11)
  - Gymnastics, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 12)
  - Gymnastics, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 13)
  - Softball Scorebooks, 1967-1971 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 14)
  - Softball Schedule, 1971 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 15)
  - Softball, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 16)
  - Softball, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 17)
  - Softball, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 18)
  - Softball, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 19)
  - Swimming + Diving, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 20)
  - Swimming + Diving, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 21)
  - Swimming + Diving, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 22)
  - Swimming + Diving, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 23)
  - Swimming + Diving, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 24)
  - Athletics, Tennis, Women's, ca. 1968 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 25)
  - Tennis, 1970 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 26)
  - Tennis JV + VAR., 1971-1972 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 27)
  - JV Tennis, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 28)
  - Tennis JV + Var., 1973-1974 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 29)
  - Tennis JV and Var., 1974-1975 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 30)
  - Tennis JV + VAR., 1975-1976 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 31)
  - Tennis JV + VAR., 1976-1977 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 32)
  - Tennis, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 33)
  - Tennis includes history of team from 1963, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 34)
  - Track and Field, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 35)
  - Track + Field, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 36)
  - Track and Field, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 37)
  - Track + Field, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 38)
  - Volleyball, 1975-1976 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 39)
  - Volleyball, 1977-1978 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 40)
  - Volleyball, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 41)
  - Women's Rosters, 1969-1977 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 42)
  - Women's Sports Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 43)
  - Women's Sports Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 44)
  - Women's Sports Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 45)
  - Women's Sports Reports, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 46)
  - Women's Sports Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (5-Womens' Sports), Folder 47)
- Publications, 1960-2007; 6; 0.66 cubic ft.
  Includes sports schedules, score books, sports press guide, Sports News and Views, and other booklets relating to intercollegiate athletics at the College /University.
  The files relating to men's general sports events consist of the seasonal sports schedules, annual score books, sports press guides, Sports News and Views, etc., and cover the period from 1960-1979, and 1985-86. The files relating to the basketball program include men's basketball guides, and the intercollegiate basketball schedules from 1970-73. The files relating to women's sports cover the period 1969-80 consisting of women's intercollegiate sports schedules. Responsibility for creating sports publications and releases rested with the community/University Relations Office.
  - 2008 American East Field Hockey Championship (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 1)
  - 43rd UAlbany Invitational, 2009 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 2)
  - Albany Athletics Newsletter, 1999 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 3)
  - Albany State Football, 1973 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 4)
  - American East and NCAA Materials, 2005-2006 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 5)
  - American East Basketball Season Officiating and Game Management Handbook, 2000-2001 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 6)
  - America East Championship Handbooks, 2001 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 7)
  - Basketball Guide, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 8)
  - Basketball Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 9)
  - Basketball Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 10)
  - Basketball Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 11)
  - Basketball Programs, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 12)
  - Basketball Programs, 1988 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 13)
  - Cosida Digest, 2000-2001 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 14)
  - Football Official Program, 1979 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 15)
  - Football Programs- The Albany State Weekly Grid Report, Sept. 25, 1971, the Albany State Weekly Football News, Oct 9- Nov 20, 1971 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 16)
  - Football Programs-: "Albany State Football News," Sept. 22-Nov. 4, 1972 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 17)
  - Football Programs: "Albany State Football News,", 1973 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 18)
  - Gameday and Sports Illustrated Publication, 2007 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 19)
  - Hofstra University 2001 Lacrosse and Softball Guides (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 20)
  - Ithaca College Football, 1981 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 21)
  - Lady Danes Basketball, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 22)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1960-1961 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 23)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1961-1962 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 24)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1962-1963 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 25)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1963-1964 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 26)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1964-1965 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 27)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1965-1966 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 28)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1966-1967 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 29)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1967-1968 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 30)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1968-1969 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 31)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1969-1970 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 32)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1970-1971 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 33)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1971-1972 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 34)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1972-1973 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 35)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1973-1974 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 36)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1974-1975 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 37)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1975-1976 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 38)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1976-1977 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 39)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC., 1978-1979 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 40)
  - Misc. Brochures, Schedules, ETC. Baseball, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 41)
  - NCAA Championships, 1990; 1992 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 42)
  - NCAA College Division III National Championship Semi-final, 1977 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 43)
  - Season Program- Great Danes Basketball, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 44)
  - "The Season Ticket: A Sports Review", 1978; 1979 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 45)
  - Southern Connecticut vs. Albany State, 1981 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 46)
  - The Student Voice, 1999 October 9 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 47)
  - Winter Sport Guide, 1971-1972 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 48)
  - Winter Sports Press Guide: Basketball, Wrestling, Swimming, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 49)
  - W. Soccer Media Guide, 2009 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 50)
  - Women's Sports Brochures, Flyers, 1969-1980 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 51)
  - Sports Team Brochures, 1983 (Box 1 (6-Publications), Folder 52)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1979-2014; 7; 10.5 cubic ft.
  This collection contains news clippings related to the athletic activities of the University At Albany's student body and the New York Giant's summer training camp. Content includes various sport scores, news stories about players/teams, and the New York Giant's training camp on campus.
  - Football News Clippings, 1979 (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - Football News Clippings, ca. 1970s-1980s (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Football News Clippings, ca. 1980s (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1996 (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1996 (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
  - Special Olympics, 1996 (Oversized 1, Folder 6)
  - Hitchcock Press News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Wrestling News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 7)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 8)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 9)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1996 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 10)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 11)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1997 (Oversized 1, Folder 7)
  - Division One, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 12)
  - Empire State Games, 1997 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 13)
  - Times Union-Giants in Training, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 14)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 15)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 16)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 17)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 18)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 19)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 20)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 21)
  - UAlbany Sports News Clippings, ca. 1998 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 22)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 23)
  - Giants News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 24)
  - Times Union-Giants Training Camp at Albany, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 25)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 26)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 27)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 28)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 29)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 1999 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 30)
  - Women's Basketball News Clippings, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 31)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 1999-2000 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 32)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2001-2004 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 33)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2001-2004 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 34)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2002 (Oversized 2, Folder 1)
  - Football News Clippings, 2002 (Oversized 2, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball Clippings, 2002 (Oversized 2, Folder 3)
  - Football News Clippings, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 35)
  - Football News Clippings, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 36)
  - Field Hockey News Clippings, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 37)
  - Football News Clippings, 2002 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 38)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2002 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Volleyball News Clipping, 2002 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Women's and Men's Cross Country News Clippings, 2002 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Women's Track and Field News Clippings, 2002 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - Men's and Women's Soccer News Clippings, 2002 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - Tennis News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball and Volleyball News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 7)
  - Golf News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 8)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 4)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 5)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 6)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2003-2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 7)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 8)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2002-2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 9)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 10)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2003 (Oversized 2, Folder 11)
  - Softball News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 9)
  - Men's Lacrosse News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 10)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 11)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 12)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 13)
  - Field Hockey News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 14)
  - Men's and Women Cross Country News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 15)
  - Men's Track and Field News Clippings, 2003 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 16)
  - Indoor Track News Clippings, 2003-2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 17)
  - Times News Clippings, 2003-2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 18)
  - Men's and Women's Soccer News Clippings, 2003-2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 19)
  - Women's Basketball News Clippings, 2003-2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 20)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004 (Oversized 2, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004 (Oversized 2, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004 (Oversized 3, Folder 1)
  - Baseball News Clippings, 2004 (Oversized 3, Folder 2)
  - Football News Clippings, 2004 (Oversized 3, Folder 3)
  - Softball News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 21)
  - Men's Soccer News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 22)
  - Volleyball News Clipping, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 23)
  - Women's Soccer New Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 24)
  - Football News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 25)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 26)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 27)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 28)
  - Times Union-Giants Training Camp, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 29)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 30)
  - Athletic Department News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 31)
  - Women's Lacrosse News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 32)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 33)
  - Men's Lacrosse News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 34)
  - Men's Lacrosse News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 35)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 36)
  - Field Hockey News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 37)
  - Men's Cross Country News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 38)
  - Women's Outdoor Track News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 39)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 40)
  - Women's Basketball News Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 41)
  - Women's Basketball News Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 42)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004-2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 43)
  - Men's Basketball News Clippings, 2004-2005 (Oversized 3, Folder 4)
  - Indoor Track and Field News Clippings, 2004-2006 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 44)
  - UAlbany Sports News Clippings, 2005 (Oversized 3, Folder 5)
  - Athletic News Clippings-Winter/Spring, 2005 (Oversized 3, Folder 6)
  - Athletic News Clippings-Winter/Spring, 2005 (Oversized 3, Folder 7)
  - Giants News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 45)
  - Giants Training Camp News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 46)
  - Softball News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 47)
  - Women's Lacrosse News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 48)
  - Baseball News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 49)
  - Department News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 50)
  - Outdoor Track and Field, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 51)
  - Men's Lacorsse News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 52)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2005 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 53)
  - Winter/Spring News Clippings, 2005-2006 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 54)
  - Winter/Spring News Clippings, 2005-2006 (Oversized 4, Folder 1)
  - Winter/Spring News Clippings, 2005-2006 (Oversized 4, Folder 2)
  - Winter/Spring News Clippings, 2005-2006 (Oversized 4, Folder 3)
  - NCAA News Clippings, 2006 (Oversized 4, Folder 4)
  - Rape Scandal News Clippings, 2006 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2006 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2006-2007 (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2006-2007 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 3)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2006-2007 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 4)
  - News Articles Part 1-LAX, Tennis,Soccer, Field Hockey, Women's Basketball, 2006-2007 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - News Articles Part 2-Misc, 2006-2007 (Box 1 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 2)
  - News Articles Part 3-Softball,Baseball,Football, 2006-2007 (Box 2 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 1)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2007 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 5)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2007 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 6)
  - Athletic News Clippings, 2007-2008 (Box 3 (7-Newspaper Clippings), Folder 7)